Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Park
  - Subseries B: Arch
    - Arch, Graffiti, circa 1980-1990 (Box 210, Folder 2)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, graffiti, circa 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking southeast, joggers, circa 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, Christmas tree, circa 1980s; wsp_ar_4_1_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 5 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, graffiti, circa 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, graffiti, wsp_ar_4_1_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, graffiti, circa 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, graffiti, circa 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, graffiti, circa 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, graffiti, circa 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 9)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail Showing Graffiti, 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Arch, Graffiti, 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 11)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 12)
      - Man Trimming Tree, circa 1980-1989; wsp_ar_4_1_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 13)
      - Washington Square Arch, Graffiti, 1980; wsp_ar_4_1_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 2, Item 14)
    - Arch, Undated (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking North, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Arch and Christmas Tree, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Arch and Christmas Tree, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking North, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking North, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Arch, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_06; color print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Arch, Detail, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 6 ½x 8 ½ inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking North, 1983; wsp_ar_4_2_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Arch, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 9)
      - People and Washington Square Arch, circa 1980-1989; wsp_ar_4_2_10 (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Arch, circa 1960-1969; wsp_ar_4_2_11; color print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 11)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking South, circa 1960-1969; wsp_ar_4_2_12; color print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 12)
      - Washington Square Arch, "Washington in War", undated; wsp_ar_4_2_13; Fishon, Robert; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 13)
      - Washington Square Arch, Looking North, undated; wsp_ar_4_2_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 3, Item 14)
  - Subseries C: Looking East
    - Looking East, 1850s-1860s, 1850-1860 (Box 210, Folder 4)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1858; wsp_le_4_4_01; drawing, 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1891; wsp_le_4_4_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7½ inches (Box 210, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, ca 1860-1869; wsp_le_4_4_03; New York Illustrated; drawing, 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Looking East, 1850s-1860s, 1850-1860; cuid17553 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Looking East, 1880s-1890s, 1880-1890; cuid17554 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Looking East, 1880s-1890s, 1880-1890 (Box 210, Folder 5)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1880-1890; wsp_le_4_5_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - Looking East, 1900-1909 (Box 210, Folder 6)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1890-1899; wsp_le_4_6_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1905; wsp_le_4_6_02 (Box 210, Folder 6, Item 2)
    - Looking East, 1900-1909, cuid17555 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Looking East, 1910-1919, cuid17556 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Looking East, 1910-1919 (Box 210, Folder 7)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1915; wsp_le_4_7_01 (Box 210, Folder 7, Item 1)
        General note
        black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches
    - Looking East, 1920-1929, cuid17557 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Looking East, 1920-1929 (Box 210, Folder 8)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1920-1929; wsp_le_4_8_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_02; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_03; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1920-1929; wsp_le_4_8_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1921; wsp_le_4_8_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_06; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_07; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 8 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1925; wsp_le_4_8_08; Rosenfeld, David; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_09; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 9 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 9)
      - Washington Square Area, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_10; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Area, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_11; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 11)
      - Washington Square Area, Looking East, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_12; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 12)
      - Washington Square Park, 1924; wsp_le_4_8_13; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7½ inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 13)
      - Washington Square Park, wsp_le_4_8_14; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 14)
      - Main Building, Washington Square Park, 1921; wsp_le_4_8_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 15)
      - Main Building, Washington Square Park, 1921; wsp_le_4_8_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 16)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1920 - 1929; wsp_le_4_8_17; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 17)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1926; wsp_le_4_8_18; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 18)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking Northeast, 1926; wsp_le_4_8_19; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 19)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1926; wsp_le_4_8_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 20)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1926; wsp_le_4_8_21; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 21)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1926; wsp_le_4_8_22; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 22)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1926; wsp_le_4_8_23; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 23)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, circa 1920 - 1929; wsp_le_4_8_24; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 210, Folder 8, Item 24)
    - Looking East, 1930-1939 (Box 212, Folder 1)
      - Main Building, Washington Square Park, circa 1930 - 1939; wsp_le_5_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 212, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Corner of Washington Square East and West 4th Street, 1930; wsp_le_5_1_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 212, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, circa 1930 - 1939; wsp_le_5_1_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 (Box 212, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Looking East, 1940-1949 (Box 212, Folder 2)
      - Main Building and Washington Square Arch, 1949; wsp_le_5_2_01; Sozio, A.F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, 19th century; wsp_le_5_2_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 212, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Washington Square East, Looking East, 1947; wsp_le_5_2_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1941; wsp_le_5_2_04; Sozio, A.F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 2, Item 4)
      - Washington Square South, Looking East from MacDougal Street, 1945; wsp_le_5_2_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 2, Item 5)
      - Main Building, New York University, circa 1940 - 1949; wsp_le_5_2_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 2, Item 6)
      - Shimkin Hall, undated; wsp_le_5_2_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 212, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - Looking East, 1950-1959 (Box 212, Folder 3)
      - Washington Square East, Looking East, circa 1950 - 1959; wsp_le_5_3_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Main Building, New York University, 1957; wsp_le_5_3_02; Gooen, Irwin; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Washington Square East, circa 1950 - 1959; wsp_le_5_3_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Washington Park Aerial View, Looking Northeast, circa 1950 - 1959; wsp_le_5_3_04; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Main Building and Washington Square Arch, circa 1950 - 1959; wsp_le_5_3_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 3, Item 5)
    - Looking East, 1960-1969 (Box 212, Folder 4)
      - Washington Square Park, 1968; wsp_le_5_4_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 210, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park and Shimkin Hall, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_le_5_4_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, 1965; wsp_le_5_4_03; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Park and Shimkin Hall, 1964; wsp_le_5_4_04; Pellettieri, Luigi; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 4, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Park South, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_le_5_4_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 4, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Park East, Looking South, 1966; wsp_le_5_4_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 4, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, 1966; wsp_le_5_4_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 4, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Park South, Looking East, 1964; wsp_le_5_4_08; Pellettieri, Luigi; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 4, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking Northeast, wsp_le_5_4_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - Looking East, 1970-1979 (Box 212, Folder 5)
      - Washington Square South, Looking East, 1970; wsp_le_5_5_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Fifth Avenue and Washington Square North, Looking South, 1979; wsp_le_5_5_02 (Box 212, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Looking East, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 212, Folder 6)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, circa 1980 - 1989; wsp_le_5_6_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 212, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Winter Scene, 1980; wsp_le_5_6_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 6, Item 2)
    - Looking East, Undated (Box 212, Folder 7)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, undated; wsp_le_5_7_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 7, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, undated; wsp_le_5_7_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 212, Folder 7, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, undated; wsp_le_5_7_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 7, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, undated; wsp_le_5_7_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 212, Folder 7, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking East, undated; wsp_le_5_7_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 7, Item 5)
      - Drawing, Washington Square Park, Looking East, undated; wsp_le_5_7_06; drawing, 11 x 14 inches (Box 212, Folder 7, Item 6)
  - Subseries D: Looking West
    - Looking West, 1800s, 1800-1899 (Box 212, Folder 8)
      - Stacked Stones, Washington Square Park, circa 1890 - 1999; wsp_le_5_8_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - Looking West, 1900-1929 (Box 212, Folder 9)
      - Washington Square West, 1905; wsp_lw_5_9_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 9, Item 1)
      - Washington Square West, Holley Hotel, 1921; wsp_lw_5_9_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 9, Item 2)
    - Looking West, 1930s, 1930-1939 (Box 212, Folder 10)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking West, circa 1930 - 1939; wsp_lw_5_10_01; Kastner, George; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 10, Item 1)
    - Looking West, 1940s and 1950s, 1940-1959 (Box 212, Folder 11)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking West, circa 1950 - 1959; wsp_lw_5_11_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 1)
      - Buses and Washington Square Arch, Looking West, 1951; wsp_lw_5_11_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 2)
      - Washington Square West, Aerial View, circa 1950 - 1959; wsp_lw_5_11_03; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking West, 1953; wsp_lw_5_11_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking West - Hayden Hall, 1947; wsp_lw_5_11_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking West - Hayden Hall, circa 1950 - 1959; wsp_lw_5_11_06; St. Claire, Phillips; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 6)
      - Washington Square West, 1953; wsp_lw_5_11_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking West, circa 1940 - 1949; wsp_lw_5_11_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 11, Item 8)
    - Looking West, 1960s, 1960-1969 (Box 212, Folder 12)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking West, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_lw_5_12_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 1)
      - Corner of Washington Place and Washington Square West, Looking West, 1962; wsp_lw_5_12_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 2)
      - Washington Square West, 1962; wsp_lw_5_12_03; Pellettieri, Luigi; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 3)
      - Washington Square South, Looking West, 1962; wsp_lw_5_12_04; Pellettieri, Luigi; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 4)
      - Fountain, Washington Square Park, 1960; wsp_lw_5_12_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Park and Washington Square Arch, 1968; wsp_lw_5_12_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 6)
      - Washington Square South and Washington Square South, 1962; wsp_lw_5_12_07; Pellettieri, Luigi; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, 1961; wsp_lw_5_12_08; Gooen, Irwin; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 8)
      - Drawing, Washington Square Park, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_lw_5_12_09; drawing, 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 9)
      - Drawing, Washington Square Park, 1973; wsp_lw_5_12_10; drawing, 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 10)
      - Truck, Washington Square West, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_lw_5_12_11; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (polaroid) (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 11)
      - Washington Square West, circa 1960 - 1969; wsp_lw_5_12_12; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (polaroid) (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 12)
      - Washington Square South, Looking West, 1962; wsp_lw_5_12_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 12, Item 13)
      - Washington Square Park, 1924; wsp_ls_6_3_03; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Washington Square South, circa 1920 - 1929; wsp_ls_6_3_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 4)
        stereoscopic photographs.
    - Looking West, Undated (Box 212, Folder 13)
      - Station Wagon Parked on Washington Square South, undated; wsp_lw_5_13_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 212, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Subseries E: Looking South
    - Looking South, 1800s (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - Mt. Washington Collegiate Institute, Washington Square, 1858; wsp_ls_6_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 1, Item 1)
        Engraving.
    - Looking South, 1900-1909 (Box 213, Folder 2)
      - Washington Square Arch and Horse-Drawn Carriages, 1900; wsp_ls_6_2_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Corner of Washington Square South and Thomson Street, 1905; wsp_ls_6_2_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Looking South, 1920-1929 (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - Washington Square South, 1925; wsp_ls_6_3_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Washington Square, Looking South, 1924; wsp_ls_6_3_02; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking South, 1924; wsp_ls_6_3_03; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Outdoor Art Show, Washington Square South, circa 1920-1929; wsp_ls_6_3_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches, copy print of stereograph (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1920-1929; wsp_ls_6_3_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 3 x 3 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Washington Square South, 1925; wsp_ls_6_3_06; Rosenfeld, David; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Looking South, 1930-1939 (Box 213, Folder 4)
      - Washington Square Park and Washington Square South, Aerial View, circa 1930-1939; wsp_ls_6_4_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1935; wsp_ls_6_4_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Snow in Washington Square Park and Washington Square South, Aerial View, 1937; wsp_ls_6_4_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Judson Building, Washington Square South, circa 1930; wsp_ls_6_4_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Looking South, 1940-1949 (Box 213, Folder 5)
      - Washington Square South and Sullivan Street, 1945; wsp_ls_6_5_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Washington Square South, undated; wsp_ls_6_5_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - Washington Square South and Wooster Street, 1925; wsp_ls_6_5_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 5, Item 3)
      - 100 Washington Square East, Looking South From Washington Square North, 1949; wsp_ls_6_5_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Looking South, 1950-1959 (Box 213, Folder 6)
      - Washington Square South, Site of Vanderbilt Hall, circa 1950-1959; wsp_ls_6_6_01; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Shimkin Hall, Washington Square Southeast, 1955; wsp_ls_6_6_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1953; wsp_ls_6_6_03; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Southeast, after Demolition, 1958; wsp_ls_6_6_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Southeast, Demolition, 1957; wsp_ls_6_6_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 213, Folder 6, Item 5)